<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sovereignty on TalkAboutBrex</title>
    <link>https://techforuk.github.io/brexchat/subject/sovereignty/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sovereignty on TalkAboutBrex</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://techforuk.github.io/brexchat/subject/sovereignty/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The single market is a good thing</title>
      <link>https://techforuk.github.io/brexchat/subject/sovereignty/fact4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techforuk.github.io/brexchat/subject/sovereignty/fact4/</guid>
      <description>The single market makes trade between EU companies easy by making all members keep to the same standards.
This means that we know the toasters produced in the UK, Germany or France are all of at least the same quality and so we don’t need to check them when they come in or out. This keeps us all safe and makes it much easier to do business in Europe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We agree with the EU most of the time</title>
      <link>https://techforuk.github.io/brexchat/subject/sovereignty/fact3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techforuk.github.io/brexchat/subject/sovereignty/fact3/</guid>
      <description>The UK has only lost a vote against a suggested EU law 56 out of 2536 times since 1999, so for around 98% of the time we agree with the EU.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We are in control of the big things</title>
      <link>https://techforuk.github.io/brexchat/subject/sovereignty/fact1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techforuk.github.io/brexchat/subject/sovereignty/fact1/</guid>
      <description>In really important areas like taxation, allowing another country to join the EU or citizen’s rights and justice, if the UK does not agree to an idea that has come from the EU, we can stop it the EU from doing it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We help decide what the EU will do</title>
      <link>https://techforuk.github.io/brexchat/subject/sovereignty/fact2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techforuk.github.io/brexchat/subject/sovereignty/fact2/</guid>
      <description>In less important areas, if the European Council want to do something they take a vote and need at least 50% of the countries to agree to it.
So, while we’re in the EU, we get to discuss and debate and play a part in deciding what all the EU countries do.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>